[Music]
[音乐]
thank you today we are going to talk
今天谢谢你，我们要谈
about building spring application but in
关于构建spring应用程序，但是
a different way than usual we are of
与往常不同的方式
course using cut lean for for the
当然使用切瘦为
language we are going to configure your
语言，我们将配置您的
spring boots in an explicit way with
spring boot 以显式方式
khufu and we are going to leverage our
胡夫，我们将利用我们的
reactive infrastructure of yeah
是的反应性基础设施
coroutines so before starting it's worth
协程，所以在开始之前值得
remaining our goals here
在这里保留我们的目标
I think the first goal is to improve the
我认为首要目标是改善
cut signal to noise ratio to make
降低信噪比
features more discoverable to make
具有更多可发现的功能
reactive easier and I truly believe that
反应容易，我坚信
explicit behavior equals less
显性行为等于少
misunderstanding or so the runtime
误解大概是运行时
efficiency will be a goal here so let's
效率将是这里的目标，所以让我们
let's start we are going to follow a
让我们开始，我们将遵循
four-step process to go from a typical
从典型的四个步骤
spring boot application developed in
Spring Boot应用程序开发于
Java to an idiomatic code in one I would
Java将惯用代码合二为一
like to make it sure that you understand
想确保您了解
that you don't have to reach to reach
您不必触及
that for to have something that is great
为了拥有伟大的东西
I mean if you just want to use spring
我的意思是如果您只想使用spring
boots like you use it in Java but just
就像在Java中使用它一样启动
with coupling as a language and exactly
结合成一种语言
the same kind of arrangement that's
相同的安排是
perfectly fine if you want to do goes a
如果您想做的话就完美了
step after and leverage the reactive
紧跟并利用反应
stack or maybe switch to co-routines
堆栈，或者切换到协同例程
that perfectly fine really
真的很好
you can stop when you want I'm just
你想我就可以停下来
showing you a way to gradually start
向您展示逐步开始的方法
from what we have currently in the Java
从我们目前在Java中获得的
world to something that I consider more
我认为更多的世界
idiomatic encoding and I think there is
惯用编码，我认为有
some very good reason to do that but
一些很好的理由，但是
really you you take what you need so the
真的，您随心所欲，所以
first step will be to switch from Java
第一步将是从Java切换到
to cut in and for that we are going to
切入，为此，我们将
use a simplified version of the
使用简化版的
application that is behind this official
该官员背后的应用程序
spring boot cut in tutorial which is
在教程中的spring boot cut是
built with spring boot GPA and cut lean
用 spring boot GPA制成，并切薄
and we are going what looks like this
我们要去看起来像这样
kind of application so let's switch
这种应用程序，让我们切换
in the code okay so I have already
在代码中好吧，所以我已经
presented a part of that during the
提出了一部分
keynote so I will go pretty fast on that
主题演讲，所以我会很快
step but it's a gradual build file
步骤，但这是一个逐步构建文件
generated thanks to status winglet IO
通过状态小翼IO生成
and it's the cut-in DSL which provides a
而插入式DSL提供了
better to complete capabilities and
更好地完成功能和
that's which interesting maybe a little
那可能是有趣的一点
bit drawback currently it's a little bit
有点缺点，目前有点
slow in terms of autocompletes but I
自动完成速度很慢，但我
know that there is some upcoming
知道即将来临
improvement so you can expect to have a
改善，因此您可以期望有
very smooth developing experience in the
非常顺利的开发经验
upcoming months and based on that
接下来的几个月，并以此为基础
theatrical class is a little bit
戏剧课有点
different to what I have presented in
与我介绍的内容不同
the keynote because here we are
主题演讲，因为我们在这里
leveraging GPA so GPA is not designed
利用GPA，因此未设计GPA
for immutable data structure so here
对于不可变的数据结构，所以这里
even if cut in push for immutable data
即使为不可变的数据而努力
structure I'm using the properties
我正在使用属性的结构
because really GPA is designed for that
因为真正的GPA是为此而设计的
we have our regular identity annotation
我们有常规的身份注释
the same kind of optional parameter will
相同类型的可选参数
default values I have presented before
我之前提供的默认值
so my controller is that one notice that
所以我的控制器是一个通知
encoding even more that in Java we
在Java中编码更多
promote the usage of constructor base
促进构造函数库的使用
injections so as I spring from 15.3 when
当我从15.3开始时
you have a single constructor it is
你只有一个构造函数
implicitly Auto wired by type and here
根据类型和此处隐式自动连线
since we have this single constructor
因为我们有这个单一的构造函数
article repository will be automatically
文章存储库将自动
inject and since whiskered clean we use
注射，由于晶须干净，我们使用
a lot immutable properties it's a good
很多不变的属性，这是一个很好的
idea to do that notice that you have to
要注意的想法是您必须
add this private key word because by
添加此私人关键字，因为
default properties are public which is
默认属性是public
not what we want here about the type
不是我们想要的类型
system I repeat it but it's very
系统我重复一遍，但是它非常
important to understand that Kathleen is
重要的是要了解凯瑟琳是
a statically typed as Java even more
静态类型更像Java
thanks to the new safety here I have
多亏了这里的新安全性
configured IntelliJ IDEA to display int
配置IntelliJ IDEA以显示int
2 displays in third type I could also
2种第三类型的显示器，我也可以
type it explicitly that's my choice but
明确键入它是我的选择，但
here I just want to see Cynthia type
在这里我只想看看辛西娅式
without having to duplicate this
无需重复此操作
information
信息
the repository is a regular one
仓库是常规仓库
Springwood application is using this
Springwood应用程序正在使用此
real application so rent application is
真正的申请，所以租金申请是
a is a top-level function because in
a是顶层函数，因为
Catalan you don't have to put a function
加泰罗尼亚语，您不必放置任何功能
inside a class and that's provided
在一个班级里提供
built-in with spring boots and you can
内置 spring boot ，您可以
basically use it by using this this kind
通过使用这种类型基本上使用它
of syntax to customize you spring good
自定义您的语法的 Spring 很好
application so that's not just as more
应用程序，而不仅仅是更多
syntactic sugar it also provides some
语法糖，它也提供了一些
configuration capabilities the blood
血液配置能力
property agent is interesting because
房地产经纪人很有趣，因为
it's a new feature or spring boot to the
这是一项新功能或 spring boot
two before spring boot to the two we had
Spring 之前的两个引导到两个
to use lazy init vowels which is not
使用懒惰的初始元音
very dramatic in Catalan because
在加泰罗尼亚语中非常戏剧化，因为
basically configuration properties in
基本上在
boot we are not managing immutable
引导我们不是一成不变的
classes because that's not super popular
类，因为它不是超级流行
in Java because that's a little bit more
在Java中，因为还有一点
verbose and as offspring would to the
冗长而后代
two spring boot managed natively
本地管理的两个Spring Boot
immutable classes and so we can use this
不可变的类，所以我们可以使用它
kind of idiomatic data class with Val
Val的惯用数据类
immutable properties and that's very
不变的属性，这是非常
good news so thanks for the spring boot
好消息，所以谢谢你的 spring boot
team for for walking on that extension
在该扩展上行走的团队
functions allow to add features hello to
功能允许向您好添加功能
add function to existing type so we use
将功能添加到现有类型，以便我们使用
that to provide more more interesting
提供更多有趣的
syntax than the regular abstract classes
语法比常规抽象类
with static methods and in my HTML
在我的HTML中使用静态方法
controller you can see that I'm using
控制器，您可以看到我正在使用
the same kind of stuff that I'm using in
我在用的那种东西
Java but with the more concise syntax
Java，但语法更简洁
and we leverage some some code in
我们利用一些代码
extensions for example you see this this
扩展，例如，您看到此
is a model so this is a very old class
是模特，所以这是一个非常古老的课程
from Spring Framework and if I try to
从Spring Framework，如果我尝试
navigate here you will see that I have
导航到这里，您将看到我有
added an extension function that is
添加了扩展功能
providing directly in spring for modules
直接在Spring 中提供模块
to provide a set operator that provide
提供一个集合运算符
basically an alias for model dot add
基本上是模型点添加的别名
attributes and that allow me
属性，让我
to use this kind of very nice syntax
使用这种非常好的语法
which is in geometric encoding to set
要进行几何编码设置
the value so really we provide the
价值，所以我们真的提供了
support for Kirkland directly in in the
直接在网站上为Kirkland提供支持
spring form of jars so we are going to
Spring 形式的罐子，所以我们要
go to the step two we are going to
转到第二步，我们要
emigrate from web and we see with GPA to
从网络迁移出来，我们发现GPA可以
web flex with ODBC to leverage our
使用ODBC的web flex以利用我们的
reactive stack to be most capable to be
反应堆最有能力成为
able to basically be immune to latency
基本上不受延迟的影响
so actually BC is a reactive SQL SPI
所以实际上BC是反应式SQL SPI
that is intended to be implemented by
旨在由
the debase driver it only depends on
仅依赖的降级驱动程序
reactive streams it is natively reactive
反应性流，它本身就是反应性的
nor thread pool here and we have drivers
也没有线程池，我们有驱动程序
for PostgreSQL my sequel h2 and
对于PostgreSQL我的续集h2和
Microsoft SQL Server on spring world you
Spring World上的Microsoft SQL Server
will consume that usually we spring data
通常会消耗我们Spring 数据
to DBC which is conceptually pretty
DBC在概念上很漂亮
close to spring that a JDBC so it's not
接近JDBC的 Spring ，所以它不是
a full-blown where em it's not GPA you
一个成熟的地方，不是GPA
directly write SQL code that can
直接编写可以
leverage the native feature of your
利用您的本机功能
database and spring that air to DBC
数据库并向DBC鼓吹
provides some very interesting feature
提供了一些非常有趣的功能
to do the object mapping so parameter
做对象映射，所以参数
biding etc and spring that out to DBC
竞标等，然后向DBC提出
comes with two AP is regular query model
附带两个AP是常规查询模型
that you usually find in spring data and
您通常在 spring data 中发现的
it also provides database Kalyan
它还提供了数据库Kalyan
functional API which is conceptually
在概念上是功能性API
close to what we have with web client so
接近我们在网络客户端上拥有的
this kind of fluent API that we to on
我们要使用的这种流畅的API
reactive types also notice it is still
反应类型也注意到它仍然
work in progress but it it's moving fast
工作正在进行中，但进展很快
so we are back in IntelliJ IDEA I'm
所以我们回到了IntelliJ IDEA
going to switch branch so I'm going to
要切换分支，所以我要
switch to the step two
切换到第二步
okay so let's have a look to what has
好吧，让我们来看看
changed we have now val properties
改变了，我们现在有val属性
because we do not have the constraints
因为我们没有约束
that is implied by GPA we are going to
GPA暗示我们将要
use air to DBC spring that a to DBC
用空气吹向DBCSpring
which as first-class support for
作为一流的支持
immutable data structure so we follow
不变的数据结构，因此我们遵循
what Kirtland designed push for we are
Kirtland为我们设计的推动力是
using immutable data classes then if I
使用不可变的数据类，那么如果我
have a look to the repository you see
看一下您看到的存储库
that I am injecting a database account
我正在注入数据库帐户
which is the API that the functional API
是功能性API的API
that spring that a JDBC provide and I'm
JDBC提供的那个 Spring ，我
writing code using this fluent API that
使用这种流利的API编写代码
which one Manu and flex and and that's
Manu和flex那是
it now let's say we would like to take
现在说我们想服用
advantage of our reactive stack and that
我们的反应堆的优势
we would like to request a remote web
我们想请求一个远程网站
service so for the purpose of this demo
服务，因此本演示的目的
I will directly create it here so I'm
我将直接在这里创建它
going to add a commands class so here's
要添加一个命令类，所以这里是
we propose is to we have this article
我们建议是要我们有这篇文章
class from a blog post and we would like
博客文章中的课程，我们希望
to request the commands from a remote
向远程请求命令
web services and we are going to add
网络服务，我们将添加
them in the article so we have this
他们在文章中，所以我们有这个
command class we are going to create a
命令类，我们将创建一个
command controller
命令控制器
so we have this command reactive
所以我们有这个反应式的命令
controller like that we are going just
像我们这样的控制器
to import so extensions need to be
导入，因此扩展名需要
imported that's important so we are
进口很重要，所以我们
basically building flags we are going to
基本上建立我们要去的标志
modify our HTML controller to add the
修改我们的HTML控制器以添加
web client so I'm going to inject a
网络客户端，所以我要注入一个
client builder which has web clients
具有Web客户端的客户端构建器
that build your type I'm going to use
建立您要使用的类型
this builder to create a client like
这个建造者来创建一个像
that I'm going to add a comments
我要添加评论
property here so a list of commands and
此处的属性，以便列出命令和
I'm going to modify this render function
我将修改此渲染功能
which is currently synchronous it just
目前正在同步它
do nothing ready to remote and I'm going
什么也不做准备去远程，我要去
to I am doing to request my web services
我正在请求我的网络服务
here I have implemented directly here
在这里我直接在这里实现
but imagine that you are requesting a
但假设您正在要求
remote web service and you know you see
远程Web服务，您知道您看到了
that now I'm rearranging web client to
现在我要重新排列网络客户端
request or remote web services and
请求或远程Web服务以及
adding this command here and now we have
在这里添加此命令，现在我们有了
a mano of rendered article so since we
自从我们开始
have a mano I'm going to transform that
有个马诺我要去改变它
from map to flat map okay to flip up the
从地图到平面地图都可以翻转
results and I'm going to modify this
结果，我将对此进行修改
part of the code to do a flat map as
代码的一部分作为平面图
well I'm going to call the random
好吧，我要称呼随机
methods and then it will be flat map
方法，然后它将是平面图
here and I modify that like that okay
在这里，我像那样修改
notice that in Kathleen when you have
请注意，当您在凯瑟琳（Kathleen）
lambdas with just a single parameter by
只有一个参数的lambda
default you can use it to refer it
默认情况下，您可以使用它来引用它
without explicitly define define it so
没有明确定义定义它，所以
last part I'm going to add modify my
最后一部分，我要添加修改我的
mustache template to be able to display
胡子模板可以显示
the commands and if I run the
命令，如果我运行
application
应用
if I made no mistake so the blog post is
如果我没有记错，那么博客文章是
really ugly because I am NOT a designer
真的很丑，因为我不是设计师
if I go to local hosts okay
如果我去当地的房东好
and I have my comments that are coming
我有即将发表的评论
from a remote web service so that's okay
从远程Web服务访问，这样就可以了
for step two now step three so we are
第二步，现在第三步，所以我们是
going to immigrate from this reactive X
要从这个反应性X移民
style API so when I say reactive X it's
样式API，所以当我说反应式X时
reactor Eric Java this kind of API to
Eric Java反应器这种API
coroutines
协程
because we are going to leverage the
因为我们要利用
coding features to be able to still
编码功能使其能够保持
leverage this nice reactive stack but in
利用这个很好的反应堆，但是
a more imperative way so kuru teens are
更迫切的方式，使库鲁青少年
coding lightweight threads are going to
编码轻量级线程将
write and blocking code in a more
更多地编写和阻止代码
imperative way I have shown you here how
我在这里向您展示了如何命令式
a reactive except e I translate to kuru
反应性的，除了e我翻译为kuru
teens so basically for a single value of
青少年基本上只为
you return nothing the API we will look
您不返回任何API，我们将寻找
like what you know in the imperative
就像你当务之急
world if you are passing some mono
世界，如果您通过一些单声道
parameters if you don't care about the
参数，如果您不在乎
laziness of mono you will just pass a
单声道的懒惰，你只会通过
value that could be retrieve itself by
可以通过自身获取的值
calling suspending function and if you
调用暂停功能，如果
want to still keep this lazy
还是想保持这个懒惰
characteristic of mono you will pass a
单声道的特点，您将通过
supplier which will be a suspended
供应商将被暂停
lambda because the suspend keyword can
lambda，因为suspend关键字可以
also be used in a lambda and that
也可以用在lambda中
conceptually very close to what we know
概念上非常接近我们所知道的
is flux or a flavor in Eric Java to
是Eric Java中的助焊剂或风味
world will translate to flow and here we
世界将转化为流动，在这里，我们
are talking about the flow type which is
谈论的是
provided with coroutines 1.2 which is
提供了协程1.2
different than the Java 9 flow container
与Java 9流容器不同
type for reference types so before
输入参考类型
trying to use that concrete in our codes
尝试在我们的代码中使用该混凝土
let's talk about this flow type
让我们来谈谈这种流动类型
last year cut clean the JetBrains team
去年削减了JetBrains团队
sets cruises our final in : 1.3
进入决赛：1.3
co-routines are years they are stable
例行程序是稳定的年份
that was only partially true I think
我认为那只是部分正确
because there was two spending functions
因为有两个支出功能
there was some API to deal with multiple
有一些API可以处理多个
value which is a channel API but I don't
值，它是通道API，但我不知道
really like it but what was missing was
真的很喜欢，但是缺少的是
this kind of flow type which is
这种流动类型是
basically the combination of suspending
基本上是悬浮的组合
functions and reactive extreme style of
功能和极端的反应风格
API and that's very interesting type
API，这是非常有趣的类型
because it's suitable for odd or cold
因为它适合古怪或寒冷
stream so when I say hot stream I means
流，所以当我说热流时，我的意思是
basically you are subscribing to a list
基本上，您正在订阅列表
of tweets and then you win concerns so
的推文，然后您赢得关注，所以
it's basically a flow of events that
基本上是事件流
emits before and after I are subscribing
在我订阅之前和之后发出
to to them cold stream are more
对他们来说，冷流更多
asynchronous iterables so basically I
异步迭代，所以基本上我
have maybe a correction of 100 elements
可能有100个元素的更正
but I want to begin processing them as
但我想开始将它们处理为
they come without putting everything in
他们没有把所有东西都放进来
memory flow is suitable for finit or
内存流适用于finit或
infinite number of elements
无限数量的元素
interestingly it deal with back pressure
有趣的是，它可以处理背压
but in a very different way that
但以一种截然不同的方式
reactive streams it just deal with that
反应流它只是处理
pressure using suspending function so
使用悬挂功能的压力
basically it will process them data and
基本上它将处理它们的数据并
then request n elements of data but if
然后请求n个数据元素，但是如果
you are you have you often do processing
你是你有你经常做处理
which is suspended it would just not
这被暂停，只是不会
request more data and that's why our
请求更多数据，这就是为什么我们的
back pressure works with flow it's a
背压与流量一起工作
little bit less powerful than reactive
比反应式动力稍差
streams but for most of the use case I
流，但对于大多数用例我
think that will be okay
认为会没事的
all operators are implemented as
所有运算符都实现为
expansions so in Louisville and flux you
在路易斯维尔扩张并让您动荡
have basically 100 of operators in flow
基本上有100个运营商在流动
you are just a single suspending correct
你只是一个悬浮的正确
methods and then all operators built in
方法，然后内置所有运算符
or custom are implemented as extension
或自定义实现为扩展
functions operators are pretty easy to
函数运算符非常容易
implement and I think that's a pretty
实施，我认为这很漂亮
interesting feature I mean have a look
我的意思是有趣的功能
to the source code of flow filter or map
到流量过滤器或地图的源代码
operator
算子
you will see it just a few lines and
您只会看到几行，
less characteristic map apparatus report
少特征地图设备报告
a synchronous operation because the
同步操作，因为
lambda is a suspending lambda so it cuts
lambda是一个悬浮的lambda，因此可以削减
you spends you don't have to use flat
你花了你不必用平
map to do operation that implies the
映射执行暗示
latency you can just use map for that
延迟，您可以只使用map
and that nap is for a flat mapping flow
那小睡是为了平面映射流程
in another flow so back to the codes so
在另一个流程中，所以回到代码中
we are going to switch branch and we are
我们要切换分支，我们是
going to this step freako routines
去这步freako例程
branch we import the differences and we
分支我们导入差异，我们
are going to do the same job of adding
将做添加的相同工作
this command command controller and make
这个命令命令控制器并
thing take take advantage of this this
事情要利用这个
kind of API but before let's have a look
一种API，但在让我们看一下之前
here so here we have now an API that is
在这里，所以在这里，我们现在有一个API
much closer to the imperative world I am
更接近我当务之急
returning a new label of article instead
而是返回文章的新标签
of mono my code is in it is basically
单声道的我的代码基本上是
close to the imperative world a big
接近命令式世界
difference between reactive and
反应和之间的区别
co-routines
协同例程
is that by default co-routines our
是默认情况下我们的例程
second sure and they provide explicit
第二肯定，他们提供了明确的
and optional concurrency while in in
和可选的并发
Reiki world it's you have to use
灵气世界，这是你必须使用
operators basically to make things
运营商基本上是做东西
second show so yeah like I said in the
第二场秀，是的，就像我在
keynotes
主题演讲
spring format 5.2 provide built-in
spring格式5.2提供内置
support for co-routines so basically it
支持协程，基本上
supports flow return types it's reported
支持报告的流返回类型
spending function for both the
两者的支出功能
annotation and functional variant of web
Web的注释和功能变体
bugs now we are going to add the very
错误，我们将添加非常
same command class nothing new here we
相同的命令类，这里没有新内容
are going to add our cou routine based
将要添加我们的cou例程
command controller
命令控制器
so it's interesting to see the
所以有趣的是看到
differences flow is a kind of decorative
差异流是一种装饰
API like stream of flags but when you
API喜欢标记流，但是当您
are inside the flow builder or in the
在流量生成器内部或
operators you are actually writing
您实际上正在写的运算符
imperative codes so here delay is a
命令代码，所以这里延迟是
suspending function that will just not
暂停功能不会
blood but suspend so blocking is bad
鲜血，但会暂停，因此阻塞是不好的
suspending is okay
暂停还可以
you can emit data so flow is a pushed
您可以发出数据，从而推动流量
based as to API so you are emitting
基于API，因此您正在发出
object that are potentially coming from
可能来自的物体
other suspending function I here and
我在这里的其他暂停功能和
that's it and I'm going to modify my
就是这样，我将修改我的
routine based HTML controller with the
基于例程的HTML控制器，带有
very same kind of stuff so I'm going to
一样的东西，所以我要
inject the same fan builder because the
注入相同的风扇生成器，因为
philosophy of the kuru routines report
库鲁例行报告的哲学
is not true
不是真的
to add new types I mean we have
添加新类型，我是说我们有
introduced a lot of new types with the
引入了许多新类型
reactive stack the idea here is to
反应堆的想法是
leverage the very same types but to
利用相同的类型，但是
provide extension functions on top of
在...之上提供扩展功能
that to provide kuru teens based API on
提供基于库鲁青少年的API
top of in addition to the regular active
除了常规活动的顶部
one so I'm going to create the client so
一个，所以我要创建客户端
the very same web client instance I'm
我是同一个Web客户端实例
going to add the commands here a list of
将在此处添加命令列表
commands and I'm going to replace this
命令，我将替换它
synchronous render extension function by
同步渲染扩展功能
something that is leveraging new
新的东西
routines so I'm going to add the COO
例行程序，所以我要添加首席运营官
routine space R under I have just two
我只有两个常规空间R
extensions to to import so you see that
导入扩展名，以便您看到
here I'm still returning around our
在这里我仍然回到我们周围
article but that's a suspending function
文章，但这是一个暂停功能
here I'm leveraging the API of web
在这里，我利用了Web的API
client where
客户在哪里
coding the extension function that
编码扩展功能
provides me an imperative API using
为我提供了使用
coroutine so if we have a logical
协程，所以如果我们有一个逻辑
navigator is there is no magic
导航器没有魔力
I'm just leveraging the co-routines
我只是利用协同程序
reactive swim interoperability to
反应游泳互操作性
transform something that return a mono
转换一些返回单声道的东西
to some things that return the plane
归还飞机的一些事情
value okay so really nothing magical
值还行，所以真的没什么神奇的
here my implementation you see it's
在我的实现中，您看到的是
imperative it is second shell by default
当务之急是默认使用第二个shell
and the interesting thing is that unlike
有趣的是，与
what I did on the reactive API I don't
我在反应式API上所做的我没有
have to modify my blog and my article
必须修改我的博客和文章
implementation because this map operator
实现，因为此地图运算符
is taking a suspending function so I am
正在执行暂停功能，所以我
allowed to call something that perform a
允许调用执行
remote call for example and here I'm
例如远程通话，我在这里
just putting around there I have this
只是放在那里我有这个
little symbol to say okay that's a
小符号说好吧，这是一个
suspending function call but I'm using
暂停函数调用，但我正在使用
that like if I was writing imperative
就像我写命令一样
code and if I just add the command here
代码，如果我只是在此处添加命令
and I run the test
然后我进行测试
okay so it's it works now now the step
好吧，现在就可以使用了
four
四
so until now we were really focusing on
所以直到现在我们一直专注于
something that will be usable shortly in
不久将可用的东西
production because spring boot to the
生产，因为 Spring 引导到
two is coming in a few weeks or months
几周或几个月内就会有两个
maybe July I don't remember a two DBC is
也许七月我不记得有两个DBC是
not production ready yet but we are
尚未生产就绪，但我们
moving pretty fast and even in spring
甚至在春季运动都非常快
that I had two DBC itself is not
我有两个DBC本身不是
production ready so support that we
生产就绪，因此我们可以提供支持
provide for spring that MongoDB
提供MongoDB的春季
Cassandra Redis with recruiting
Cassandra Redis的招聘
extensions is production ready and is
扩展程序已经可以生产了，并且
part of the spring boot to the two so
spring boot 的一部分要两个这样
with a new SQL part you can totally use
有了新的SQL部分，您可以完全使用
routine based persistence in a
基于常规的持久性
production really way here with the step
真正的生产步骤
four we are really entering in the
四，我们真的进入
experimental incubating part of the of
的实验孵化部分
the of the torque okay so I really would
的扭矩还可以，所以我真的会
like to make it clear that until now we
想明确一点，直到现在我们
have on something that is almost
几乎有东西
production ready here we are on some
生产准备就绪，我们在这里
incubating work that may graduate and be
可能会毕业并正在培养的孵化工作
usable in production reading mode but we
可用于生产阅读模式，但我们
are not here yet so I'm going to talk
还没来我要谈谈
about stuff that have been that are
关于那些已经是
currently incubating in spring foo so
目前在春季foo孵化，所以
spring foo is an incubator intending to
spring foo是一个打算孵化器
mature experimental feature before the
成熟的实验特征
inclusion in spring farmer in spring
纳入春季农民
projects like from our food and data in
像我们的食物和数据中的项目
fact the coup routines report was part
政变例行报告是事实的一部分
of spring foo before graduating to
foo毕业之前
spring data answering from work so
spring data 从工作中回答
that's a good example and values feature
这是一个很好的例子和价值观特征
used actually that you find in spring
实际上使用了您在春季发现的
from all 5.2 where part of spring foo
从全部5.2中， Spring foo的一部分
and khufu is the main remaining feature
而胡夫是主要的剩余特征
that is currently incubating in spring
目前正在春季孵化
foo Kofu for Kathleen and functional is
凯特琳（Kathleen）的foo Kofu和功能是
a minimalist efficient and explicit
极简高效和明确
configuration model for spring boots
spring boot 的配置模型
that leverage is occurred in DSL and I'm
这种杠杆作用发生在DSL中，
going to show you concretely what it
要具体向你展示它
means in term of history in fact I add
实际上，就历史而言，
the ID to walk on Kofu last year here at
去年在Kofu上行走的ID
spring a
Spring
so I started a few months after the walk
所以我走了几个月后才开始
on the khufu 0.0 that ex version so this
在khufu 0.0的那个ex版本上
was initial experimentation a lot of API
最初的实验是很多API
breakage a lot of changes I also tried
破损我也尝试过很多变化
to walk on Jeff foo for Java and
在Java的Jeff foo上行走，
functional to provide basically exactly
提供基本准确的功能
the same thing applied to Java but there
同样的事情也适用于Java，但是
was too much too much noise in the DSL I
DSL中的噪音太多了
mean Java is too verbose to be able to
意味着Java太冗长而无法
use this approach so that does not mean
使用这种方法并不意味着
that Java will not provide an API to
Java不会提供API来
configure Springwood in a programmatic
以编程方式配置Springwood
way in the future but I just want to
未来的方式，但我只想
focus on Kofu right now and maybe later
现在或以后专注于甲府
you will have other kind of api to
您将拥有其他类型的api
configure boot cuff you when dot o was
在点o是
released this week and it brings spring
本周发布，带来 Spring
and missus reports in addition to spring
和小姐报告除了 Spring
web flux and khufu 0.2 is work in
网络通量和khufu 0.2在
progress and we are working with the
进步，我们正在与
community wisdom body which is in this
在这的社区智慧体
room on spring security DSL on
Spring 安全DSL上的房间
supporting actuators and supporting
支撑执行器和支撑
spring that a JDBC Redis Cassandra
Spring ，JDBC Redis Cassandra
Andrew configuration and on graphic we
安德鲁配置和图形我们
are support where somebody from the
在某人的支持下
community is currently providing help so
社区目前正在提供帮助，因此
we are going to see concretely what that
我们将具体看到
means so we are going to gradually
意味着我们将逐步
transform this application into an
将此应用程序转换为
application that is leveraging khufu so
利用胡夫的应用程序
khufu is basically just an API that you
khufu基本上只是您的API
will adhere to configure so basically
基本上会坚持配置
I'm adding the dependency to have the
我正在添加依赖项以具有
GSL but what is important was understand
GSL，但重要的是要了解
is that underneath i'm just leveraging
是我只是在利用
the exact same infrastructure of spring
Spring 完全相同的基础设施
boot and spring farmer but exposed in a
靴子和春季农夫，但暴露在
different way and the purpose of Kofu is
Kofu的不同方式和目的是
to be able to configure everything
能够配置一切
explicitly so we are leveraging the
明确地，所以我们正在利用
spring boot configuration infrastructure
Spring Boot配置基础架构
but there is no auto configuration there
但那里没有自动配置
is just explicit configuration that you
只是您的显式配置
will configure with ease DSL
轻松配置DSL
and you will see that we are going to
您会看到我们将
use less annotation so this I just
使用更少的注释，所以我只是
remove it because we don't need it I'm
删除它，因为我们不需要它
going to remove the annotation and
将要删除的注释和
provide another way to configure my
提供另一种配置我的
application so here I just removed the
应用程序，所以在这里我只是删除了
annotation on a properties I'm removing
我要删除的属性上的注释
the annotation on repository side and
仓库侧的注释和
I'm going to the blog application here
我要去这里的博客应用程序
I'm removing that as well okay in plate
我也将其删除
and I'm going to create the application
然后我将创建应用程序
using this DSL so really ggs the
使用这个DSL，所以真的ggs
application DSL is release the main
应用DSL是释放的主要
entry point of khufu here I'm just going
我要去的胡夫入口点
to configure spring boots in an explicit
在显式配置 spring boot
way so do I want to create a standard
这样我想创建一个标准
application a servlet one to use some
应用一个servlet来使用一些
cat or a reactive one to use nettie here
猫或反应性的人在这里使用nettie
we are going to use the crew teens
我们要用船员的少年
reports so I want to build on top of the
报告，所以我想建立在
reactive infrastructure then let's say I
反应性基础设施然后让我说
want config the configuration properties
要配置配置属性
so I'm going to configure it like that
所以我要像这样配置
so I'm specifying the properties here
所以我在这里指定属性
and I will leverage a cutting name
我会利用一个易名的名字
parameter to have this kind of nice
参数具有这种不错的
readable way of defining my
定义我的可读方式
configuration properties prefix the ID
配置属性以ID为前缀
is read to reuse the vocabulary and the
阅读以重用词汇表和
building blocks of spring boots but
spring boot 的组成部分，但
specified in a more explicit way the
以更明确的方式指定
application will be just run like that
应用程序将像这样运行
okay nothing magical that just a
好吧，没什么神奇的，只是
programmatic way to run spin good
以编程方式运行自旋良好
infrastructure and I'm going to specify
基础设施，我要指定
my configuration so I'm going to add my
我的配置，所以我要添加我的
data configuration so let's let's take a
数据配置，让我们来看一下
little bit of time to see what's going
一点时间看看发生了什么
on here you may be mostly know the
在这里，您可能大部分都知道
slices of spring boots that allow you to
spring boot 片，让您
go to use data slices or web slice to be
去使用数据切片或网络切片
able to run your waiting Russian tests
能够运行您等待中的俄语测试
faster do mocking etc but these are
更快地进行嘲讽等，但这是
predefined static slices okay
预定义的静态切片可以
there is a data one the web one and this
有一个数据，一个网络，这个
art we define here you are in charge to
我们在这里定义的艺术，您负责
defend the granularity that you want to
捍卫您想要的粒度
create your own configuration slices so
创建自己的配置片，以便
here I'm going to specify my own beans
在这里我要指定自己的beans
and the part of the spring goodness a
还有 Spring 的美好
structure that is related to the data
与数据相关的结构
configuration but I am using this kind
配置，但我正在使用这种
of technical speed but if you want to do
技术的速度，但如果您想做
some more functional splitting like
一些更多的功能拆分，例如
Oliver in this module it torque it's
奥利弗在这个模块中它的扭矩
totally possible so here I'm defining
完全有可能，所以我在这里定义
beans okay this is AB inst yourself from
bean 好吧，这是AB公司自己
Spring Framework here I'm specifying
我在这里指定的Spring Framework
that article repository should be ensure
该文章存储库应确保
be created and it will be automatically
被创建，它将自动
the parameters of the constructor will
构造函数的参数将
be automatically auto wired noticed that
被自动自动连线，注意到
I've cooled creates my been using a
我冷却后就开始使用
supplier okay like that but here I have
这样的供应商还可以，但是我在这里
chosen to just and I can get a reference
选择公正，我可以得到参考
to the rabbit here I'm just doing like
到这里的兔子我就像
that at would be supposed to SQL will
在应该SQL将
trigger basically that's a shortcut to
基本上触发这是
configure all the beans that are
配置所有的bean
required for air to DB supposed to go
送往DB的空气所需的空间
SQL so what that's basically what's
SQL，这基本上就是什么
being good does with auto configuration
自动配置很好
but here that's explicit I'm defining a
但是在这里，我要定义一个
listener and I'm going to say that in
听众，我要说的是
this application I want to enable the
我要启用此应用程序
data configuration okay that's explicit
数据配置好了，很明显
now the big part I'm going to migrate
现在我要迁移的大部分
our annotation base a web layer to
我们的注释基于一个Web层
something which is leveraging the
利用的东西
functional variants of web flops so I'm
网络拖鞋的功能变体，所以我
going to transform my controller which
要改变我的控制器
has both the mapping you see this at
两者都有您在上看到的映射
request mapping slash API slash article
请求映射斜杠API斜杠文章
and the implementation of the
和实施
Unlimited's
无限的
to something that only contains the
到只包含
ending part and the route will be
结束部分，路线将是
externalized
外在化
so i'm going to rename article
所以我要重命名文章
controller to article under i'm going to
我要去的文章的控制器
replace this implementation by
将此实现替换为
this one again I have to import
这一次我必须导入
extensions to be able to use them so
扩展以便能够使用它们
it's really different instead of having
真的有不同，而不是
this this annotation and this flexible
这个注释和这个灵活的
signature I'm some and so on something
签名我是某某某某
that is more functional I have a several
那更实用我有几个
requests as an input parameter and are
请求作为输入参数，并且
returning a suspending as I have a
返回暂停，因为我有一个
suspending function that will return a
暂停函数将返回一个
server response okay and this is the
服务器响应还可以，这就是
reactive API where I have some guru
我有一些专家的反应式API
teens extensions so that's okay for
青少年扩展名，所以可以
article and I will do the same things
文章，我将做同样的事情
for the common controller so I'm going
对于通用控制器，我要去
to rename it to commands under I'm going
将其重命名为我要执行的命令
to replace the implementation with the
用
functional variants so the commands
功能变体，因此命令
under like that I'm going to do the same
在这样的情况下，我将做同样的事情
for the HTML controller I hope I need to
对于HTML控制器，我希望我需要
rename it so HTML under okay I replace
重命名它，以便可以替换HTML
the implementation with that one okay
那个实现就可以了
and now I'm going to add the water
现在我要加水
because now I have just the under
因为现在我只有
implementation and I want to add my
实施，我想添加我的
route so here I'm leveraging functional
路线，所以我在这里利用功能
routing things so basically it allows me
路由的东西基本上可以让我
to define so you have an API that
进行定义，因此您拥有一个API
provides values requests predicates you
提供价值要求谓词
can combine them with and and or
可以将它们与和和或
operators you can use nested request
可以使用嵌套请求的运算符
predicates you can even use dynamic code
谓词甚至可以使用动态代码
with if for loops to create your routes
使用if for循环来创建您的路线
and it's not just a syntactic sugar
不只是语法糖
imagine you want to develop in Kirkland
想象你想在柯克兰发展
a CMS or e-commerce solution where the
CMS或电子商务解决方案，其中
roots come from something that is
根源是
created via the back office so you only
是通过后台创建的，因此您只
have that in the in the database and
在数据库中有
this allow you to create roots
这允许您创建根
dynamically rather than having
动态而不是拥有
everything statically a define with no
一切都是静态的，没有
annotation so it's much more than just a
注释，所以它不仅仅是一个
syntactic sugar or another way to write
语法糖或其他书写方式
that it's more flexible mechanism that
更灵活的机制
allow you to do more powerful things so
让你做更强大的事情
and here I have a single root you can
在这里我有一个根
create multiple rooters combine them so
创建多个rooters组合它们，以便
I'm just showing users a simple
我只是向用户展示一个简单的
arrangement now we are going to leverage
现在我们要利用的安排
this nice rotor and unless by creating
这个很好的转子，除非通过创建
our our server configuration and that
我们的服务器配置以及
that begins to be even more interesting
变得更加有趣
here so like I said it's explicit so I'm
在这里，就像我说的是明确的，所以我
going to define my server config
要定义我的服务器配置
configuration slice or module not sure
配置片或模块不确定
what is the right name yet but I'm
正确的名字是什么，但我是
defining the beans so I'm defining
定义beans，所以我在定义
article under HTML under control on your
HTML在您的控制之下的文章
beans that will be all injected by type
将按类型注入的bean
new feature from sweep swing from oxide
氧化物清除摆动的新功能
the two we now can create bin by using a
这两个我们现在可以通过使用
function top level function reference
功能顶层功能参考
because basically this Broadwater
因为基本上这个布罗德沃特
function could be be seen as a kind of
功能可以看作是一种
bean factory a bean soup layer so I'm
bean 工厂 bean 汤层，所以我
just using a reference to that top level
仅使用对该顶级的引用
function and all the parameter will be
功能，所有参数将是
automatically injected and there is no
自动注入，没有
reflection here it's all done at compile
反射到这里，一切都在编译完成
time by a colon then I'm going to
时间冒号，然后我要去
configure more high-level stuff and the
配置更多高级内容，然后
stuff that is related to swing boot
与秋千靴有关的东西
infrastructure by declaring that I have
通过宣布我有基础设施
a web flag server and here I specify
一个Web标志服务器，在这里我指定
that I will specify the codec explicitly
我将明确指定编解码器
while in spring boot auto configuration
在 spring boot 时自动配置
mechanism you will have some codecs that
机制，您将拥有一些编解码器，
are created automatically based on the
是根据
dependencies you have here you are
你在这里的依赖
responsible to define
负责定义
to define the codex to define their
定义食典来定义他们的
orders and you can also configure that
订单，您还可以配置
to specify that you want autocomplete
指定您要自动完成
and basically its interests is that
基本上它的兴趣是
everything is discoverable you don't
一切都是可以发现的
even have to go to the documentation you
甚至必须转到您的文档
have full discoverability here and it's
在这里具有完全的可发现性
much more than that because you have you
不仅如此，因为你拥有你
can specify customize the engine to say
可以指定自定义引擎说
that you want to use Tomcats not not on
您要使用Tomcats而不是
cat here but jetty or other engine you
猫在这里，但码头或其他引擎
can basically divine filters you can
基本上可以用神圣的过滤器
even configure your course so it's it's
甚至可以配置您的课程，就是这样
pretty powerful no not here you have a
非常强大，不，不，您在这里
you have also the mustache support to do
你也有胡子支持做
the view rendering and I think like that
视图渲染，我认为是这样
I'm going to add the latest slice which
我要添加最新的切片
is my client configuration okay so here
我的客户端配置可以吗，所以在这里
again I'm in charge of configuring the
再次，我负责配置
codecs I'm going to enable this
编解码器，我将启用它
configuration in my in my application so
在我的应用程序中配置
I enable server configuration I enable
我启用服务器配置
client configuration I can even
客户端配置我什至可以
configure the logging by specifying the
通过指定配置日志记录
level again everything is discoverable
再次将一切都发现
and that's that's it so I think that
就是这样，所以我认为
should be okay so if I try to run my
应该没问题，所以如果我尝试运行我的
application
应用
okay so you see it start pretty fast and
好吧，所以您看到它开始非常快，
my web my blog post is still not very
我的网站我的博客文章仍然不是很
nice but you see that intimate
很好，但是你看到那贴心
functionality that's that works pretty
相当不错的功能
well now let's say I want to update my
好吧，现在假设我要更新我的
tests because with the khufu approach
测试，因为使用胡夫法
you don't you can create some custom
你不可以创建一些自定义
application context so you will do
应用程序上下文，因此您将
things a little bit differently so
事情有点不同
basically you don't need any kind of a
基本上你不需要任何一种
unit specific support for spring you are
您对春季的单位特定支持
just going to program thing you know do
只是去编程你知道的事情
things in a programmatic way so here
以编程方式进行操作
what I do let me close that thing here
我所做的让我在这里结束那件事
what I do is that I am building just for
我要做的是我只是为了
the purpose of my test a custom
我测试风俗的目的
application where I would just integrate
我将集成的应用程序
the slice the configuration slices that
切片配置切片
I need so I'm just integrating server
我需要，所以我只是集成服务器
config and client config not that I
配置和客户端配置不是我
config and I'm going to mock theatrical
配置，我要模拟戏剧
repository via mock which is the
通过模拟存储库
equivalent in Korean world to mojito and
在韩国世界相当于mojito和
that's--it's okay so it's really
没关系，所以真的
important to see that if you organize
重要的是要知道如果你组织
your configuration configuration slices
您的配置配置片
in a granular with the right granularity
以正确的粒度
you are in control or creating custom
您可以控制或创建自定义
application just for the purpose of your
只是为了您的目的而申请
tests with the granularity that you want
以所需的粒度进行测试
if you want to build just application
如果您只想构建应用程序
tests we will just reuse the app which I
测试我们将重复使用我所使用的应用程序
have defined here okay here I do not try
已经在这里定义好了，在这里我不尝试
to create a custom application as just
创建一个自定义应用程序
doing a regular integration test with
与进行常规集成测试
the existing application I run it I get
我运行它的现有应用程序
a context and then I am able to do some
上下文，然后我就可以做一些
assertions because what return
断言，因为返回什么
application doctrine is just an
应用学说只是一个
application context so again this kind
应用程序上下文再次如此
of syntax may sounds not familiar yet
的语法听起来可能还不熟悉
but underneath you are using all
但在下面，您正在使用所有
underneath features and types that
在功能和类型下面
spring provide
春季提供
ok so let's finish the presentation with
好的，让我们用以下内容结束演示
more information so if you like this if
更多信息，如果您喜欢，如果
you like this kind of configuring spring
你喜欢这种配置Spring
boots and a more functional way in a
靴子和更实用的方式
more explicit way feel free to have a
更明确的方式可以随意拥有
start with a spring foo repository you
从spring foo仓库开始
can also contribute things really the
也可以真正贡献力量
community start to contribute very
社区开始做出很大贡献
interesting feature like the spring
像 Spring 一样有趣的功能
securities report and other features
证券报告及其他功能
like that so feel free to come try it
这样，请随时尝试
send feedbacks simple request really we
发送反馈简单的要求真的我们
are in in at a time where you can
在你可以的时候进来
significantly influence this project and
对这个项目有重大影响，
you can provide features now the
您现在可以提供功能
foundation are almost stable and we need
基础几乎稳定，我们需要
to add support for other parts of the
增加对其他部分的支持
spring Buteyko system so feel free to
Spring 的Buteyko系统让您可以随意
come and and contribute I would like to
来贡献我的力量
finish by summary about the status
最后总结一下状态
because we have seen some things that
因为我们看到了一些东西
are that will be available shortly in
不久将可用吗
production and other things that are
生产和其他东西
more incubating so what is production
更多的孵化，什么是生产
reading whispering boot to the two is
阅读耳语到两个引导
the web flux and the ASO gets routine
网络流量和ASO变得常规
reports the spring that are reactive
报告反应性的Spring
MongoDB Redis Cassandra codes in
MongoDB Redis Cassandra代码在
extension so this is a production ready
扩展程序，这样就可以生产了
and this cool routines API are just
这个很酷的例程API只是
another way to consume directive API
使用指令API的另一种方法
that we have started to provide
我们已经开始提供
whispering phenoxide work-in-progress
耳语中的酚盐在制品
that means that we are working on that
这意味着我们正在努力
and it may be available short term in
它可能在短期内可用
new production release states there is a
新产品发布说明有一个
coup routine repository so like you have
政变例行资料库
this reactive code repository interface
此反应式代码存储库接口
in spring data it could be interesting
在 spring data 中可能会很有趣
to have the very same capabilities with
具有完全相同的功能
the crew teens in addition to the
船员们除了
functional API so there is a dedicated
功能性API，因此有专门的
issue for that feel free to to add your
问题，随时添加您的
plus one obviously a 2d BC and spring
再加上一个明显的公元前2d和 Spring
attached to the BC need to reach the GS
连接到BC需要到达GS
stage to be integrated in spring boot
集成在 spring boot 中的阶段
and usable in a production ready stage
并且可以在生产准备阶段使用
and Kofu is still incubating
Kofu还在孵化
so again feel free to contribute to send
再次随意为发送做贡献
us feedback that's really something that
我们的反馈实际上是
at some point I really would like to
在某个时候我真的很想
have supported in a production ready
支持生产准备
stage we are not here yet so that's the
阶段我们还没到这里，那就是
right time to send you feedback say that
正确的时间给您发送反馈说
you are interested or not and contribute
您是否感兴趣并做出贡献
maybe what you would like to see support
也许您想获得支持
it here so thanks a lot and yeah thanks
在这里，非常感谢，是的，谢谢
[Applause]
[掌声]
[Music]
[音乐]